

### Husein Muftić

• Address: Založje Odred Sretno 6, 71370, Breza, Bosnia and Herzegovina

Email address: husein muftic@hotmail.com \ Phone number: (+387) 62528494

Q Upwork: https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~01a6dfec0d05c890eb

Github: <a href="https://github.com/husein625?tab=repositories">https://github.com/husein625?tab=repositories</a>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/husein-muftić-79655815b/

**Gender:** Male **Date of birth:** 25/10/1998 **Nationality:** Bosnian-Herzegovinian

### **ABOUT ME**

I am Front-End developer with more than 2 years of experience working on various projects through different companies. I am specialized in frontend development, maintenance, bug fixing and web optimization.

The best features in my work as an engineer are that I strictly follow the requirements of the client, strictly meet the deadlines, I am always available, I give suggestions for improvements if necessary, I work only in a safe and verified environment. I can very easily adjust to working in a team. On the other hand, I work very well as an individual. I am very communicative and I ask everything in detail in time before starting work.

I do frontend development, especially Angular. I have more than 2 years of experience in the Angular framework. This includes experience and knowledge in HTML, CSS, SCCS, Bootstrap. On the other hand, I am familiar with backend technologies, especially .NET Core and MSSQL as a database.

Happy to work on new creative ideas and projects, with my knowledge and experience your success is guaranteed.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

[ 01/02/2021 - 04/06/2021 ] **Frontend Developer** 

### Eduati

City: London

### Main activities and responsibilities:

Working in this position as a frontend developer I gained a lot of experience and knowledge. There I worked on the development of a landing page, and I maintained the already existing system. In addition, I worked on the development of an E-learning platform consisted of a student, employer side and course provider. Our team worked with the scrum methodology, and we used Jira as a project management tool. https://www.eduati.cloud

[ 04/06/2021 - 01/10/2021 ] **Frontend Developer** 

### **GLOBE CONTRACTING**

City: Fredonia, Arizona **Country:** United States

### Main activities and responsibilities:

On this position I worked as a frontend developer in Angular. My responsibilities were maintenance existing system and development of a new accounting system.

# [ 01/09/2021 - 01/01/2022 ] **Frontend Developer**

### **Digital Krikits**

City: Hampshire

Country: United Kingdom

**Main activities and responsibilities:**Development of system for lawyers.

We used SCRUM methodology in development. The team was consisted of about ten

people.

https://wakkl.com/en/home

# [01/01/2022 - Current] Frontend Developer

### **Pulses**

City: Dubai

**Country:** United Arab Emirates

Main activities and responsibilities:

Working on maintenance and improvements of systems in production.

In most of the system is used Al. Our system is used in Dubai Mall and BMW Center Dubai

https://www.pulses.ai/

# [ 05/02/2022 - Current ] Angular Developer

### Pickwings AG

City: Baar, Zug

**Country:** Switzerland

### Main activities and responsibilities:

In this role, I am working on the development of system called Huuper.

The system is consisted of few parts. Landing page, Company, Driver and Admin side.

System will be used all across the Europe.

https://huuper.web.app

# EDUCATION AND TRAINING

# [ 10/2017 - 05/2021 ] **Software Engineering**

### International University of Sarajevo

Address: Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

# [ 12/10/2020 - 10/11/2020 ] **Software Engineering Internship**

Infinity Mesh <a href="https://www.infinitymesh.com">https://www.infinitymesh.com</a>

Address: Robot 7A, Zmaj od Bosne b.b., 71000, Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Bosnian

Other language(s):

**English** 

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1** 

### **DRIVING LICENCE**

Cars: B

### **OTHER SKILLS**

### **Programming Skills:**

-Software Engineering skills:

- Angular/ JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- HTML/CSS/SCSS
- ∘ .Net Core/ C#
- Adobe XD/ Figma/ InVision
- Scrum Methodology
- Git (Github/ Gitlab/ Bitbucket)